

M.Hassan Zaheer

Data Scientist

How to reach me:

Primary Cell:

0348-0236400

Secondary Cell:

0333-2396938

Email:

mhassanzaheer@gmail.com

Linkedin:

@mhassan-zaheer

Adress:

Amina square, Garden East, Karachi

Professional Skills

Flutter App Development,
API Integration, Firebase, Flask,
C#, JavaScript, HTML/CSS,
Python, SQL, Data Scraping,
Graphic designing Automation,
Machine learning, Programming,
Data Modeling, Client Handling,
Data Analysis, Data
Management, Data Analytics,
Data Visualization · Data
Science, Project Management.

Personal Profile

Data Scientist with a BSCS degree and two years of experience in the relevant field. Skilled in machine learning, data analysis, automation and Power BI dashboarding. Seeking to apply my expertise and creativity in the computer science Field.

Career Summary

Senior Analyst

Dec 2021 - Present

EY (Ernest & Young)

- Efficient production planning and Automation of a Production Plant.
- Developed and deployed finance models to optimize business processes.
- Designed interactive dashboards on Power BI
- Developed user-friendly interfaces.

Data Analyst Intern

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

Frontier Technology Institute

- Web scraping and product development.
- Worked on some concepts which include:
 - Data pre-processing
 - Data Analytics
 - Automation
 - API Integration
 - Freelancing

Educational Training

PAF - KIET

BS-CS, Jan 2019 - Jan 2023

- CGPA: 3.73 / 4.00
- Electives: Machine Learning, Information Security
- Awarded the Directors
 Honor Award for academic excellence.
- Developed an app for medical diagnosis as a final year project.
 - Used ML and DL models to predict based on the input data.
 - Integrated APIs from various sources.
 - Hosted the model on the cloud.

Certifications

Flutter App Development

Jawan Pakistan Aug. 2021- Mar. 2021

Web Development

Skill Development Council Feb. 2021- Aug. 2021

Graphic Animation Program

Skill Development Council Sept. 2020- Apr. 2021

Data Science

Frontier Technology Institute Jan. 2021- Jun. 2021

Software engineering

NED University Nov. 2019- May. 2020

Founder of Frontier Technology Institute Cell: 0322 6197150

Ayman Rehan

Manager (Analytics) at EY Cell: 0300 8295271

일반건축물대장(갑)

(2쪽중제1쪽)

고유번호				412851050	0-1-0796000	명칭	강촌마을 유치원동	호수/가구수/세대수 0호/0가구/0세대								
대지위치	경기도 고양시 일산동구 마두동 지번									로명주소 경기도 고양시 일산동구 강석로 152 (마두동)						
※대지면적	선면적 0 m				※지역 일반주거지역			※지구	1	※구역						
건축면적	용적률 185.76 ㎡			난정용 연면적	주구조		주용 철근콘크리트조		<u>-</u> 유치원	층수	지하: 1층, 지상: 2층					
※건폐율	※건폐율			<u>=</u>	0 %	높이		8.91 m	지붕	경사슬라브	부속건축물	동 ㎡				
※조경면적	※조경면적			공지·공간 면적	m [*]	※건축선 후	퇴면적	m	※건축	추선후퇴 거리		m				
	건축물 현황									소유자 현황						
구분	충별	구조		용도		면적	(m³)	성명(명칭) 주민(법인)등록t (부동산등기용등록	<u>번호</u> (번호)	주소	소유권 지분	변동일 변동원인				
주1	지1	철근 콘 크리트	조	유치원		1	73.52	곽노은		_ _ 경기도 고양시 일산구 마두동 739 한심 _ 유치원	<u> </u>	1996.4.24.				
주1	1층	철근콘크리트조 유치원		유치원		185.76		570823-2****		유치원 		소유권이전				
주1	2층	철근콘크리트.	 조	유치원		1	73.52			- 이하여백 -						
		- 이하여백 -							* 0] 건축물대장은 현소유자만 표시한 것입	나다.					

이 등(초)본은 건축물대장의 원본내용과 틀림없음을 증명합니다.

고양시 일산동구청장



발급일: 2023년 8월 10일

담당자: 전 화:

고유번호 4128510500-1-07960000											명칭 호수/가구수/세대수 강촌마을 유치원동					수 0호/0가	구/0세대
대지위치 경기도 고양시 일산동구 마두동					번 796					도로명주소 경기도 고양시 역					일산동구 강석로 152 (마두동)		
구분	성명 또	는 명칭	면허(등	※주차장					승강기			허가일 1990.10.17		0.10.17.			
건축주	선경건설(주),코오롱건설(주)		110111-0****			 본 옥나	. 4	옥외	인근	 면제	승용	용 대	비상용	대	착공일		199010
설계자	(주)창우종합건축사사무소, 종합건축가전				11					근제		※ 하수처리시설		사 용승 인일	199	93.6.29.	
공사감리자	(주)진아건축도시종합건축사 사무소,가전				자주	식	대 ㎡	3 대 ㎡	대 m [*]		형식	형식			관련 주소		
공사시공자 (현장관리인)	선경건설(주),코오롱건설(주)		110111	-0*****	기계	식	대 mi	때 m	대 m [*]	대	용량	량			지번		
※제로에너지건축물 인증 ※건축			물 에너지효율등급 인증			※에너지성능지표(EPI) 점수			※녹색건축 인증			※지능형건축물 인증]		
등급 등급						검		등급	급		등급						
에너지자립률	0 %	1차에너지 소요량 6 (또는 에너지절감률) kW		0 kWh/m²(%)	※에너지	너지소비총량		인증점수	<u> </u>		젇	점 인증점수 점					
유효기간:~ 유효기간:			~			0 kWh/ml 유효기간: .			~ .		유효기간:	~		도로명			
내진설계 적용 여부	물 특	특수구조 건축물 유형]						
지하수위 G.L m 기초형식 설							설계지내력(지내력기초인 경우)					설계 해석법					
변동사항																	
변동일	변동내용 및 원인						변동일			변동내용 및 원인					그 밖의 기재사항		
2001.3.21. 2005.5.16.																	

[※] 표시 항목은 총괄표제부가 있는 경우에는 적지 않을 수 있습니다.